

PROFILE 90s child, I grew up with the Internet. Since then, I have always been fascinated by the web and its architecture. To satisfy my creativity and curiosity, I naturally turned to digital communication. After 4 years, I decided to learn a new complementary skill. I am now a junior front-end developer & digital communication manager.

EXPERIENCES

HEAD OF DIGITAL COMMUNICATION

August 2018 - March 2022

French Apples & Pears Association, Toulouse FR

In charge of digital development for the french label Vergers écoresponsables (apples, pears, peaches, apricots)

DIGITAL COMMUNICATION

Development of the label's social media strategy with the following objectives: visibility & brand awareness

COMMUNITY MANAGEMENT / CONTENT CREATION

Creation of editorial schedules, content writing, graphic design, managing and moderating social medias, setting up paid campaigns and drafting of performance reports

MEDIA WATCH

Curation of written, audiovisual and digital press for the members' weekly press review

OTHERS

Website animation, social media training, photography, video capture and editing

COMMUNITY MANAGER

February 2017 - February 2018

Agence Pure, Toulouse FR

In charge of digital development and social media strategy

DIGITAL COMMUNICATION

Development of the digital strategy for 7 clients

COMMUNITY MANAGEMENT / CONTENT CREATION

Managing and moderating social medias with creation of editorial schedules, content writing, setting up paid campaigns and drafting of performance reports

SKILLS

HARD SKILLS Ruby on Rails • ES6 JS • SQL • Sass MVC pattern • Git • Github • HTML • CSS • Bootstrap • React Wireframing (Figma, Sketch) • Suite Adobe (Ps, Ae, Pr) Graphic Design • Social Medias

SOFT SKILLS Product Mindset • UX/UI Basics

Collaboration Workflows • Curious • Creative • Eager to learn Team spirit • Project & Content management • Analyzing needs • Adaptability • Autonomy • All-rounder

PROJECTS

REMPIL - RoR app

March 2022

Le Wagon, Full Stack Bootcamp

We made an application as part of our end of bootcamp project for Rempil: a turnkey solution for reusable containers

ROYAL PARTY - RoR website

March 2022

Le Wagon, Full Stack Bootcamp

We made a "Airbnb clone" project called Royal Party where you can rent castles for your private events

AHELE

September 2019 - June 2021

Founder, Toulouse FR

Ahele was an online store for women

EDUCATION

FULL STACK BOOTCAMP

October 2021 - March 2022

Le Wagon, 100% remote

MASTER DIGITAL CONTENT MANAGEMENT

2014 - 2016

EJCAM, Marseille FR

BACHELOR'S DEGREE PROJECT MANAGEMENT

2011 - 2014

ICT, Toulouse FR

LANGUAGES

FRENCH + ENGLISH

C1

GERMAN

A1